# JUSTIN BARLOWE

#### *WEB DEVELOPER*

### CONTACT

justin.barlowe@proton.me

919-935-2292

Cameron, North Carolina

/in/justinbarlowe/

/Justin-Barlowe

**CAREER OBJECTIVE** 

Experienced paramedic with 10+ years of service seeking a transition into web development. Combining problem-solving skills and attention to detail from emergency medical services with a growing knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I am eager to contribute to a dynamic web development

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science Web Development Bellevue University 2024

Bellevue, Nebraska

Relevant courses

Enterprise JavaScript I & II Node.js

**Associates of Science Emergency Medical Science** Favetteville Technical Community College 2020

Fayetteville, North Carolina

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Paramedic.

Harnett County EMS January 2023 - current / Lillington, North Carolina

# Paramedic Supervisor

Fort Bragg EMS 2022 - 2023 / Fort Bragg, North Carolina

# Paramedic Supervisor

**Cumberland County EMS** 

2014 - 2022 / Fayetteville, North Carolina

# Combat Medic

United States Army

2018 - 2013 / Fort Stewart, Georgia

## SKILLS

JavaScript NoSQL MongoDB Git/Github Agile/Scrum

Node.js HTML/ CSS